[
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "5⁴",
    "correctAnswer": "625",
    "otherAnswers": ["725", "525", "575", "675"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "0⁰",
    "correctAnswer": "1",
    "otherAnswers": ["0", "2", "10", "-1", "Não definido"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "2⁽⁻¹⁾",
    "correctAnswer": "0,5",
    "otherAnswers": ["1", "2", "-1", "-1", "0", "-2"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "3½",
    "correctAnswer": "~1,73",
    "otherAnswers": ["3", "1.5", "6", "1.41"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "5⁽⁻²⁾",
    "correctAnswer": "0,04",
    "otherAnswers": ["0,5", "0,4", "0,05", "0,25", "0,025"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "10⁶",
    "correctAnswer": "10.000.000",
    "otherAnswers": ["100.000", "10", "1.000.000", "10.000.000", "0,000001"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "10⁽⁻⁸⁾",
    "correctAnswer": "0.00000001",
    "otherAnswers": ["0.000000001", "0.000001", "0", "1", "0,0001"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "6² + 5²",
    "correctAnswer": "61",
    "otherAnswers": ["55", "56", "57", "67", "37"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "∛3",
    "correctAnswer": "~1,44",
    "otherAnswers": ["1,5", "1,45", "~1,73", "1,77", "1,7"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "∛8 × 3²",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "otherAnswers": ["12", "20", "16", "14", "11"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "√144",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "otherAnswers": ["13", "16", "14", "11", "18"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "√225",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "otherAnswers": ["25", "35", "5", "55"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "√0",
    "correctAnswer": "0",
    "otherAnswers": ["1", "-1", "1", "Não definido"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "√225",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "otherAnswers": ["25", "35", "5", "55"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "3³ + √121 - 1",
    "correctAnswer": "37",
    "otherAnswers": ["38", "36", "35", "31"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "√1 + √4 + √9",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "otherAnswers": ["5", "14", "16", "17", "8", "9"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "1¹ + 2² + 3³",
    "correctAnswer": "32",
    "otherAnswers": ["20", "10", "9", "26", "18"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o resultado da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "√144 - 2 + 5²",
    "correctAnswer": "35",
    "otherAnswers": ["55", "125", "15", "75"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o valor de \"n\" da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "2ⁿ = 64",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "otherAnswers": ["5", "4", "7", "8", "3", "9", "12"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o valor de \"n\" da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "4ⁿ = 16",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "otherAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "16"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual o valor de \"n\" da expressão abaixo?",
    "item": "2ⁿ + 5 = 21",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "otherAnswers": ["7", "5", "11", "12", "17"]
  }
]
